(Sheldon:)They gave us science, democracy,
(Sheldon:)and little cubes of charred meat
that taste like sweat.
Penny? Penny?
(Sheldon:)Penny?
(Penny:)Hey. What's up?
(Sheldon:)The mean Indian lady tried
to make me eat lamb.
(Sheldon:)Congratulations.
(Sheldon:)Pizza night will now
be at your apartment.
(Sheldon:)Order one.
(Penny:)Oh, I'm sorry, honey,
(Penny:)I'm meeting Amy and
Bernadette for dinner.
(Penny:)But you're welcome
to tag along.
A girls' night?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I don't know
if I'm up for an evening
(Sheldon:)talking about rainbows,
unicorns and menstrual cramps.
(Penny:)Okay, suit yourself.
(Penny:)We'll probably be
trashing Priya a little.
(Sheldon:)Shotgun.
(Penny:)Okay, I'd like
to propose a toast
(Penny:)to a wonderful
girls' night out.
(Amy:)Fair warning--
we can get ca-razy.
(Bernadette:)Yeah. Last week we smoked cigars
and pretended to be dragons.